7:30 right now.
[现在是早上7：30]
Coming up,a recap of the  disturbing story...
[我们将对一则惊人的消息作简要报道]
...Skeletal remains  discovered by a group
[一些六年级小学生在Anacostia发现了]
of sixth grade students  in anacostia.
[人类尸体遗骸]
The remains have not yet  been identified,
[目前还没有确认尸体的身份]
according to police, and there's no word as to
[警方声称 他们还不了解]
whether foul play is suspected.
[尸体是否开始腐烂]
Dale,the word most repeated  by the young witnesses
Dale 我们采访者中最年轻的一位
we spoke to: "Horror,"as in," it looked like a horror movie."
用的最频繁的词是恐怖 就像看恐怖电影一样
A body left to rot in the  filth of a back alley
将尸体留在小巷的垃圾堆中等待其腐烂
with little regard  for human life.
这是对生命很不尊重的行为
-I hate press cases. -Yes,sir.
-我讨厌媒体关注的案件 -是 先生
More than three cameras  show up,
同时有三台摄像机报道
and some homicide detective  kicks it up to his captain,
某个私家侦探把它丢给了他的老板
who kicks it up to the chief, who kicks it to the fbi.
老板踢给了他的头头  那个头头又把这踢给FBI
You--bang--kick it down to me.
然后你Bang一声又把它踢给我
Which I thank you for,sir, the opportunity.
谢谢你 长官 给我这个机会
Booth,I want this closed.
Booth 我希望能尽早结案
I don't want to pick up  next sunday's post
我可不希望拿起下周日的报纸
and read,"church kids find  mystery corpse "
写着“教堂一男孩发现了一名
dressed for halloween. Fbi remains clueless."
万圣节打扮的神秘尸体 而FBI至今没有进展"
I guarantee you won't read  that,sir,okay?
我向你保证 你不会看到的
I'm on it.
交给我吧
Bones?
I got here as soon  as I could.
我以最快速度赶来
Yeah,great. Thanks for coming.
谢谢你能来
Did I pull you from  anythinimportant?
我没有把你从什么重要的事那拉出来吧?
A 9,600-year-old caucasoid  female skeleton
一具9600年历史的高加索女子尸骨
was found inthe kunlun mountains  in china last month.
上个月在中国的昆仑山被发现
An international investigation  is underway.
正在进行国际性的调查
I'm contributing stress-marker  analysis.
我负责分析压力痕迹
I think you're going to find  this very interesting,too.
我觉得你会认为这个也很有趣的
What the hell is he wearing?
他穿的是什么？?
It's lightweight.
看上去很轻
composite.
是合成物
I think it was some kind of  sexual bondage suit.
我认为应该是一种捆绑作用的外套
And there's that bag.
还有那个包
That's full of maggots.
长满了蛆
Looks like cellulose in there,
里面看上去有纤维素
degraded from bodily tissues  and decomposing fat.
是从身体组织和脂肪分解出来的
And maggots.
还有蛆
Tibial plateau fractures  and ground disturbance
从胫骨处的破裂和地面裂缝看来
suggest total body impact.
身体接受过冲击
Okay,so did he jump, or was he pushed,bones?
那么是他自己跳下来 还是被推的 bones?
That's what we have  to figure out.
这就是我们要知道的
We can take the skeleton in,
我们可以把骨头带回去
give you a report maybe  after next week.
下周后给你报告
Oh,no,you don't have to  solve the whole case,
你不用帮我解决整个案子
just tell me if I'm looking  at a murder.
只要告诉我这是不是一起谋杀就可以了
Maybe pull a quick I.D.?
也许再帮忙确认一下他的身份?
Don't use your charm  smile on me.
不要把你的迷人微笑用在我身上
What? It's a mark of respect, that's all.
为什么？这只是表示尊重而已
Epiphyseal union with the  diaphysis on the wrists,
骺骨区域和腰部的长骨
knees and ankles suggest  the victim was
还有膝盖 脚踝都说明受害者
between 14 and 18 years old.
在14-18岁左右
1.6 meters tall, a very slight build,
1.6米高 身体纤细
suesting he was at the  younger end of the scale.
他也许只有14岁
That tracks with the bag.
研究过包了
The degraded cellulose we  found is a graphic novel.
分解的纤维素是图画小说
-A what? -It's a comic book.
-什么? -是本漫画书
-I never read comic books. -Really?
-我从来不看漫画 -真的?
Oh,I had you pegged  for a graphic novel nut.
我还以为你很喜欢呢
The face and cranial vault  are badly fractured.
脸部及头盖骨凹陷处毁坏很厉害
Blows to the parietal  have sent radiating
腔壁的爆裂导致
fracture lines betwtween  the mid-frontal
在拱比中前部和前部的裂痕
and anterior temporal  buttresses.Why?
为什么？
Star wars,star trek, stargate,
[Star wars] [star trek stargate] (电影名称)
battlestar galactica.
[battlestar galactica] (电视剧名称)
Focusing,gentlemen.
集中注意力 先生们
Conclusion: Brutal assault killed him.
结论：残忍的殴打是死因
He was dropped...
这么说他是...
after he was already dead.
在死后被丢下来的
His killer wanted it to  look like a suicide.
杀手想让这看上去像是自杀
Let's get his dentals  into the ncic,
把他的牙齿样本送去NCIC
see if we can find a match.
看看是否能找到匹配的
Zack,call stockholm  and beijing.
Zack 打电话给stockholm 和北京
Our research data on the other  thing is going to be delayed.
我们在那方面的研究会延误
It's warren granger, age 17.
他叫warren granger 17岁
Seventeen? Small for his age.
17？对他这个年龄来说个头很小
Yeah,well, he was home-schooled,G.E.D.
他是自学的 G.E.D.
Obtained last summer.
去年夏天得到的
Mother and stepfather  reported him missing
住在这个街区的母亲和继父
from this very block  two months ago.
2个月前报警说他失踪
Hey,listen,bones,you know. if you want to sit this part out,
bones 如果你不想插手
hey,I know you got some ancient  chinese bones waiting.
我知道你还有古老的中国尸骨要处理
No,I'm on this now.
不 我现在处理这个
Looks like every other house  in the neighborhood.
和街区里的其他房子没什么不一样
Every family has its secrets, bones.
每个家庭都有他们自己的秘密 Bones
This was warren's room.
这是warren的房间
No one's been up here since the  detective first looked it over.
自从侦探调查过这里以后 就没有人上来过了
The news said there was hardly  anything left of him.
新闻说他几乎不剩什么肉了
Can you think of anyone who  might have wanted to...
你能想得出谁会想要...
harm warren in any way?
那样伤害warren吗？
He was always by himself.
他总是一个人
No friends,no enemies.
没有朋友 也没有敌人
Spent all his time up here with  his comic books and toys.
一直一个人在这上面看漫画玩游戏
He was a lonely kid.
他是个孤单的孩子
Boy died before he even  had a life.
他在还没有享受到生活之前就死了
I really thought he had  just run away.
我真的以为他是逃走了
We tried.
我们试过
Tried to get him out of  this place,
试过让走走出房间
into some kind of real life.
过真正的生活
I even got him a job at the  bowling alley,but...
我甚至在保龄球馆给他找了份工作...
he just spent all his money  on this stuff.
但他只是把钱都花在这些东西上
Unbelievable.
难以置信
That's quite the collection  of comic books.
这里收藏了很多漫画书
Hodgins said that the cellulose  mass was a graphic novel.
Hodgins说纤维素团是一本漫画书
He sent it to angela for  analysis and recovery.
他把它送到了Angela那里 去做分析和复原
-Sweet. -Sweet?
-好厉害 -好厉害?
This is batman #127,featuring  the hammer of the thor.
这是蝙蝠侠127 讲的是hammer of the thor
This is worth about 300 bucks.
这大概值300美金
Booth,are you a nerd?
Booth 你是个书呆子吗？
First of all,you mean geek,
首先 你说的是怪人
and no,I'm not,okay?
而且 我不是
It's quite normal for an american male to read comic books.
对于一个美国男性来说 看漫画是很正常的
I find it hard to believe
我很难相信你
you have anything inommon  with warren granger.
与warren granger会有相同之处
Oh,you mean isolated, with an inner secret life?
你是说孤僻并有秘密的生活?
No,I'd say you were more  like warren.
我觉得这点你比我像warren
zack discovered some significant  hairline parry fractures
zack发现了些显著的细长裂痕
on the right and left ulnae.
在左右尺骨处
It's his arms.
是他的手臂
I know ulna means for an arm--
我知道尺骨是手臂的意思--
I pay attention.
我有在听
I also know that parry  fracture means
我还知道这意味着
that the kid fought back, bones.
那孩子有反击 bones
Small of stature,a geek,
体形小 怪人
and he fought back.
还有反击
Yeah,he also got thrown  from a roof.
对 他还被从屋顶上摔下来
There's nothing but games  on here.
这里只有游戏
There's no journal.
没有日志
There's no documents, nothing personal.
没有文档 什么私人的东西都没有
What did he at his desk?
他在这个台子上做过些什么?
I mean,there's a light; the rug is worn.
这里有灯 毛毯也被抹掉了
He used this area for something.
他用这块地方做了些什么
What was it?
是什么呢?
It's probably where he read  his comic books.
也许是他看漫画的地方
I think warren sat here  and wrote,longhand,
我觉得warren坐在这里写草书
with a ballpoint pen.
用一支圆珠笔
That's pretty retro  for a geek.
这对一个怪人来说很正常
Well,at least we know where he  got the idea for a costume.
至少我们知道他服装的来源了
Citizen 14.
Superhero.
超级英雄
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:marcella 校对:小 多 时间轴:YTET-bayang23
[识骨寻踪]-[BONES] 第一季 十二集
Hodgins dried out  and separated the pages.
Hodgins把页面弄干并且分开了
I digitized them  and adjusted for ink seepage.
我把他们扫进电脑里并调到墨水状态
Was this printed commercially?
这书是用作商业用途的吗?
No,it's a prototype, it's handmade.
不 是原形 手工的
That's what he was writing  at his desk.
这是他在桌前面写的
A comic book starring himself.
一本以他自己为主角的漫画
A shy,adolescent young man  renders himself as a superhero.
一个害羞 青春期的男孩 把自己描绘成一个超级英雄
Alone in that room all the time,
一直一个人在那个房间里
maybe warren got consumed  by his own fantasy.
也许warren因为自己的幻想而迷惑了
You think he was actually out  fighting crime?
你觉得他自己出去和犯罪作斗争？
Well,the boy got beaten  to a pulp
这孩子被打成肉酱
while wearing his superhero outfit
还穿着超级英雄的服装
in the heaviest crime area  of D.C.,Bones.
并且在D.C.犯罪最多的地区 Bones
As you know, being a writer yourself,
你自己的也是个作家
dr.Brennan,warren granger's  comic book
Brennan教授 warren granger的漫画书
could be infused with his real  life fears and conflicts.
可能会灌输给他真实的恐惧和斗争
Especially in the case of  an adolescent writer.
特别是对于青少年作家来说
Can you retrieve  any more of this?
你能复原其他的吗?
Yeah,sure.
当然
Fine.What's our next step?
下一步该怎么办?
Oh,we'll go see if warren  had any friends
我们应该查下warren是否有朋友
his mother didn't know about.
而且是她母亲不认识的
Wait a minute--
等一下--
warren granger was the skeleton  corpse those kids found?
warren granger是那具孩子发现的尸体?
Yeah.
是的
Sounds like you were close.
听说你们很亲密
How long was he lying there  all dead like that?
他死后在那里躺了多久？
Well,for a while.
有一会儿了
How well did you know warren, mr. Ellis?
你对warren有多了解 Ellis先生?
He came in here all the time.
他一直过来这里
You know,he,uh, knew his stuff.
他很在行这些
He was a nice kid.
他是个好孩子
Really nice guy.
真的很好
Something you're not  telling us?
你是不是在隐藏什么？
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
Well,you seem a little nervous.
你看上去有些紧张
You just told me that  someone I know
你才告诉我 我认识的某人
is this rotting skeletal corpse  that's been all over the news.
就是新闻都在报道的尸骨
What do you expect?
你还希望我有什么反应?
Is there a party upstairs?
楼上是不是有聚会?
Oh,it's the,uh... doomsday group.
那是... doomsday团队
I rent it out thursday nights.
周四晚上我把房间出租
Hey,wait,um, warren was actually one of them.
等一下 warren也曾参加过他们
Oh,well,you know, that's a handy thing to remember.
这是个很有用的事
Anything else you forget  to mention to me?
你还有什么忘了告诉我吗？
No,that's it,I think.
不 就这点了
hey,excuse me, this is a private function,
这是私人地盘
so,good-bye.
再见
Go ahead-- don't let me stop you.
继续--不要因为我停下来
What are you doing,exactly?
你们在干什么?
Guys,this is actually a  real live woman--
这是一个活生生的女人--
something you don't see often.
是你们一般看不到的
And like I said,
就像我说的
this is a private function, so...
这是私人地盘 所以...
hey,it's the fbi, all right?!
他们是fbi
Just turn it off for a minute, please?
把它关上几分钟可以么?
Fbi?
I'm yasutani the terrible.
我是恐怖的yasutani
I speak for this clan.
我是这里的头
Okay,well,we'd like to  ask you a few of questions,
我们想问你一些问题
if you're not too,
如果你们不是很
busy.
忙的话
The costumes, the social awkwardness,
服装还有怪异的社会
the active fantasy life, he victim would fit
还有幻想的生活 受害者会觉得
right into this sub-grouping.
很容易适应这种地下组织
Okay.Hey,mr.,Uh... yakitori the horrible?
mr... 恐怖的yakitori?
-What's your real name? -Jeremy kuznetsky.
-你的真名叫什么? -Jeremy kuznetsky
Do any of you people know  warren granger?
你们有人认识warren granger吗?
Something happened to warren, didn't it?
warren发生什么事了 是吗?
Warren's dead.He was murdered.
Warren死了 是谋杀
No,I never said anything about him being murdered.
我从没说过他是被谋杀的
Neither did the press.
媒体也没说
Yeah,well,obviously, if you're the fbi,
但是很明显 你是fbi
he was murdered.
所以他是被谋杀的
You guys don't investigate  people getting hit by a bus.
你们可不调查被公车撞死的人
Okay,great--
你们谁在什么时候最后看到warren?
when's the last time any of  you have seen warren?
Couple months ago, when he left.
几个月前 他离开的时候
-Left? -Citizen 14 was one of us...
-离开? -14号公民曾是我们中的一个...
until he went psycho,and bugged out,
知道他发神经 然后退出
-called us all sers. -"Pathetic fantasists."
-称我们为装腔作势的人 -"可悲的幻想家"
-Was he wearing his,outfit? -His identity,yeah.
-他穿着自己的制服吗? -是的
Why do you wear these  identities?
你们为什么要穿着些衣服?
For the game.
为了游戏
How serious do you take  the game?
你们把这个游戏看得多重?
It's only fun if you take  it seriously.
只有你严肃看待它才会觉得有趣
-You always play here? -You know,
-你们一直在这里玩? -知道吗
"play" is not exactly the  right verb,okay?
"玩" 不是一个准确的词
-Don't even try to explain it to them. -Shut up!Who cares?!
-不要费心向他们解释 -闭嘴！谁还关心这个！
Didn't you hear?! Warren is dead!
你没听到吗?! Warren死了!
It's okay,minnow!
没关系的 minnow!
-What's your name? -Blue minnow.
-你叫什么? -Blue minnow.
Okay,guys, when I ask your names,
当我问你们名字的时候
I want the ones that your  parents gave.
我要你们父母给你的名字
Abigail zealey.
Abigail zealey
Citizen 14 was my partner.
14号公民是我的搭档
Is that what you call warren? Citizen 14?
这是你们怎么叫warren的? 14号公民?
Citizen 14 was my partner. Warren was my friend.
14是我的搭档 Warren是我的朋友
It was a little more than that.
不止这些
Hey,hey,hey.
I don't like to judge  an entire subculture,
我不喜欢评论地下文明
but those people gave me  the creeps.
那些人让我发毛
Because they are creepy.
因为他们很恶心
What?Those kids at the school  weren't your good old harmless,
那些孩子不是以前的那种
tutor-you-in-math geeks.
教你数学的怪人
They were the  set-the-school-on-fire geeks.
他们是烧学校的怪人
Dark nerds.
黑暗系怪人
Columbine nerds.
夸张的怪人
Columbine?
夸张?
You think yasutani the terrible  is actually capable of murder?
你认为恐怖的yasutani会谋杀?
I think they get high, they play these games,
我觉得当他们兴奋起来 玩那种游戏
they lose their grip  on reality.
然后脱离现实
They start to believe that  they are these characters.
他们就开始觉得他们就是那些角色
You mean like warren, out fighting crime?
你说像warren出去和罪犯斗争?
You know,maybe warren  and that guy,
也许warren和那个人
the leader,yasuhama...
领导yasuhama...
-yasutani the terrible. -Yeah,yasutani the terrible.
-恐怖的yasutani -对 恐怖的yasutani
Maybe him and that guy,
也许他和那个家伙
they got into this magic fight, and it became real.
开始幻想的争斗 然后成了现实
So you're saying it wasn't  warren who was murdered.
所以你在说不是Warren被杀
It was his character,
而是他的角色？
citizen 14.
14号公民
They're so delusional, they don't even know
他们如此无知
that they've committed a crime.
以至于不知道自己犯罪
I'll get hodgins to see
我会让hodgins查一下
if there's any signs of drug  use in warren's hair.
Warren的头发里有没有用过毒品的痕迹
I've managed to get some of  the text back from this panel.
我成功地从这版上复原了些文本
Cheerful little tyke.
清晰度还不错
The writer was in pain.
作者很痛苦
I don't think it was purely
我不认为这纯粹是因为
the adolescent angst  of the outsider.
青少年的排外心理
In fact, I'd go so far as to say
事实上我得说
it wasn't mere  psychological pain.
这是不小的心理痛苦
He's afraid of actual,
他害怕现实的
physical death.
身体上的死亡
Can you really pull all that  information from a comic book?
你真的能从漫画里看出这些?
Absolutely.
当然
All writers reveal more  of themselves
所有的作家都比想象中更
than they intend on every page.
投入在自己的作品上
You know,I never bought all  that english 101 stuff.
要知道 我从没有买过完整的101个版本
Sometimes a river is  just a river.
有时 事情本来就是这样
All due respect, but my writing,
我无意冒犯 但我的书
for example, is pure fiction.
举个例子来说 就是纯粹的小说
Dr.Brennan,I fear you reveal  much more of your world-view
Brennan教授 恐怕你还没有意识到
in your writing  than you realize.
你流露出了许多你对世界的看法
Such as?
例如?
Such as archaeologists make  good administrators
例如考古学家会成为很好的管理者
because they enjoy tedium.
因为他们喜欢单调的生活
Such as artists are doomed  to a life of loneliness
例如艺术家注定要一生孤独
because they aren't able to think  beyond instant gratification.
因为他们没有办法期待长时间的喜悦
Such as fbi guys are hot and  angela here wants
例如fbi男生都很性感 这里的angela
-to have sex with me. -Yeah.
-想和我上床 -对
All I'm suggesting is that, while dr.Goodman goes through
我只是想说Goodman教授分析
warren's writing,we should  concentrate on the hypotheses
warren的作品时我们应该专注于
that are congruent with  forensic evidence.
它与法医的证据一致
I'm going to take another look  at warren granger's remains.
我想再看一下warren granger的遗体
In the last 24 hours,
在过去的24小时里
I've read several dozen comic  books and graphic novels.
我读了许多漫画和图画小说
Hodgins find any sign of  drug use?
Hodgins找到用毒品的迹象了吗？
No.
没有
They're quite interesting, the graphic novels,especially.
他们很有趣 特别是图画小说
After you clean the bones, look for scoring
等你把骨头清理后 找一下
on the occipital condyle  and the inferior nuchal line.
枕骨和颈背处的痕迹
They're basically a retelling  of the greek myths
他们既是都是在重述怪人的故事
with all superheroes standing  in for hercules:
充满了像大力士那样的超级英雄
Half god,half human.
半神半人
Be very careful here.
这里要很小心
X ray shows fragmentation of
X光显示出这里有
the cervical vertebrae consistent  with sharp force trauma.
颈部椎骨破裂还有物理外伤的痕迹
Invulnerability,super strength,
所向无敌 巨大力量
heightened senses, telekinesis.
超级感应 心电感应
I would love to have some  of those powers.
我也希望有这些能力
Why?
为什么？
I don't really know. Is it an odd desire?
我也不清楚 这愿望很奇怪么？
Why fantasize?You're smart.
为什么要幻想？你已经很聪明了
In some ways, my intelligence is a handicap.
某种意义上来说 我的智力是种残疾
For one thing,I'm weird.
一 我很奇怪
For another,I tend to make  people feel stupid,
二 我老是让人们觉得自己很愚蠢
and they resent me for it.
他们因为这个对我很不满
I suspect it's the same  for superpowers.
我觉得对于大力士也一样
The victim was stabbed here  at the base of the spine.
受害者再脊骨处被刺伤
The spinal cord was severed.
脊髓流出
That's what killed him.
这是死因
I'll clean the bones  and try to match
我会清洗骨头
a weapon to the damage done.
然后找到匹配的凶器
Which will make you a real hero  in the real world.
这能让你在真实世界中成为真正的英雄
in this restored panel from  the second and final volume
在这个第二和最后一本书的样板上
of citizen 14,we begin to see  a female presence,
我们可以看到出现了一个女主角
beautiful,ethereal,
美丽 高贵
which he calls the opalescence.
他叫她opalescence.
A girl he literally  can't approach.
一个他在现实中无法接近的女孩
What if warren was only...
如果warren只是...
supplying his own  masturbatory materials?
提供了一个自己手淫的对象呢？
Yes.Lonely adolescent boy.
是的 孤独的青少年
But the story moves beyond  that dimension.
但是故事超过了这个尺度
Here we see the idealized  female opalescence
在这里我们看到这个理想化的女性
cowering before  a dark male figure
在一个黑色的形象面前被制服
referred to only as the twisted.
书中这个人叫twisted
So citizen 14 wants to rescue  the opalescence from the twisted.
所以14号公民想从twisted手里 把opalescence救出来
Could this be warren's mother  and stepfather?
这会是warren的母亲或继父吗？
Elements of romantic love.
有浪漫爱情的元素
This girl surrounded by blue.
这个女孩被绿色环绕
And one of those comic book  geeks was a blue girl.
他们曾说过 漫画怪人中 有一个女孩喜欢蓝色
I'd say she's definitely  worth questioning.
那我觉得应该好好问问她
Blue minnow.
Blue minnow
That's your alter ego.
这是你的化名
Abigail zealey is my alter-ego.
Abigail zealey才是我的自我
Did you,abigail,
abigail
have a relationship with  warren granger,
和warren granger有亲密关系
or did the blue minnow have a  relationship with citizen 14?
或是blue minnow和公民14 是否有亲密关系?
-Or any combination thereof. -Neither.
-或者其他的关系 -都没有
Warren had a girlfriend  at capital bowl.
Warren在capital bowl有个女朋友
What's the girlfriend's name, abby?
那女孩叫什么 abby?
He never told us her name.
他从来没提到过她的名字
It was just a physical thing.
这只是身体上的
And it was almost over.
而且都快结束了
Warren and I had a connection.
Warren和我相互联系着
He couldn't deny that.
他否认不了这点
Before he disappeared,
在他失踪前
he gave me his entire neil  gaiman collection--
他把整套neil gaiman都给了我--
his favorite work beside his own.
除了自己作品外他最喜欢的一套
In his own work,he describes  a woman known as the opalescence.
在他自己的作品里 有一个叫opalescence的女性
Do you believe that's  supposed to be you?
你认为那是你吗？
What do you think?
你们觉得呢？
We think it's another  girl entirely.
我们觉得那是完全另一个人
Does that bother you?
这让你很困扰吗？
Okay.
Maybe the others told  you i'm obsessed,I know.
也许其他人说我很痴迷
Because they never got  warren like I did.
那是因为他们没有像我一样了解Warren
He was right.
他说得没错
They are posers.
他们就是装腔作势的人
And warren wasn't?
但warren不是？
Warren believed.
Warren相信
He believed in truth.
他相信事实
He believed in doing  what was right.
他相信要做正确的事
He was citizen 14.
他就是citizen 14
Citizen 14 is real.
Citizen 14是真实的
Warren didn't fit in  with the others?
Warren和其他人合不来?
I just said warren  was better!
我刚才说过了 warren要更好！
He was a really nice guy.
他真的是个很好的人
Were you aware that  jeremy kuznetsky
你知道 jeremy kuznetsky
and kenneth vert have police records?
和kenneth vert有犯罪记录吗？
Yeah.
是的
It's nothing interesting, though.
没什么有趣的
It's,like, vandalism and trespassing.
破坏公物还有私闯私人地区
You can't take them seriously.
不能把他们看得太严肃
What,as criminals?
什么？看成犯罪？
As anything.
看成任何事
Okay,well,what would  be interesting?
那什么才有趣？
As a crime.
犯罪
Something that took courage.
需要勇气的
Something that meant  something.
有意义的东西
Like murder?
谋杀？
Yeah,like murder.
对 像是谋杀
Warren granger on the night  he died,
在Warren granger死的那晚
wearing his costume.
他穿着自己的戏服
Start the sequence.
开始播放
Cause of death was  a severed spinal cord.
死因是一些戳伤
We can rule out abigail  zealey as the killer.
我们可以排除abigail zealey
How do you figure?
为什么?
Abigail doesn't have enough  strength
Abigail没有足够的力量
to sever warren's spinal cord  with one blow.
来造成warren's脊髓处的伤
What about his step-dad?
那他的继父呢?
Or the other kids  at the comic shop?
或者漫画店的其他孩子？
Well,if the physicality  of the murderer
如果凶手的身高是
is between five-ten  and six-two,
5.10英尺至6.2英尺之间
I'd say yes to them all, depending on the weapon.
是的 所有人都有可能
God,what could he have done  to make somebody
他做了什么让某人
so angry at him?
对他这么生气？
Zack's cleaning the bones now.
Zack正在清洗骨头
Maybe we'll find something  that we've missed.
也许我们可以找到遗漏的东西
-What are you reading? -I'm doing research.
-你在看什么? -我在作研究
by reading a comic book?
研究漫画书?
Intensely allegorical  modern myths.
深刻的现代寓言故事
You're reading bugs bunny, man.
你在读废书
On the surface,yes, but if you dig deeper,
表面上是的 但是深入的话
the subtext becomes apparent.
隐语就会很明显
The conflict is representative  of the darwinian struggle
其中的冲突代表了达尔文有关
between avians and mammals  for dominance.
鸟类和哺乳动物争夺自然主导权的理论
Based on bugs giving daffy duck  a cigar made out of dynamite?
来自一只虫给了达费鸭一支炸药做了雪茄？
Yeah.
对
And then here, he explodes,
然后他爆炸了
but not really.
但不是真爆炸
You have a problem,my man.
你搞出问题来了
What?
什么？
Looks like you degraded  the bones.
你好象分解了骨头
Impossible.
不可能
It's only a four-percent  peroxide solution.
只有百分之四的过氧化氢
Then what's that bubbling  and pitting on the periosteum?
那在骨头上面冒泡和挖坑的是什么东西？
Four-percent solution  wouldn't cause that.
百分之四的溶液不会产生这种事
So,what,it's some kind of  systemic deterioration?
那是全身性的系统退化？
The intertrochanteric crest is  almost totally eaten away.
转子内部差不多都被侵蚀掉了
What do you think it is?
你觉得是为什么?
This kid was sick.
这孩子生病了
Smell that?
闻到了吗?
Yes,I do.
是的
You know what that is, bones?
你知道那是什么吗 bones?
Wax,popcorn...
蜡 爆米花...
feet,deodorant...
脚 臭味...
that is america,bones.
这才是美国 Bones
Keep your bowling ball  in the car?
把你的保龄球放在车子里了？
Oh,you know,I figure we ask  a few questions
我觉得我们可以问几个 有关warren granger的问题
about warren granger, maybe bowl a few frames.
也许打几回
Nothing like a little sport  to take the edge off.
没有比运动来得更容易放松了
-This is not a sport. -How do you figure?
-这不是运动 -为什么?
There's no physical benefit.
没有体能上的好处
So it's really like golf.
就像高尔夫一样
It's not a sport,
不是体育运动
it's an activity.
只是活动
Could you please,bones, maybe just for once
Bones 能不能就一次
try not to piss everyone  off around you?
不要让你身边每个人都对你很生气？
Yeah,sorry.
抱歉
Are you good at this sport?
你对这运动在行吗？
My average was over 200, less than two opens per game.
我的平均值是在每场比赛起码200
One match,I had 211 strikes  out of 431 shots,
有场比赛 我431个击球有211个全中
29 opens in 39 games.
39场比赛里有29个开
What does that mean?
什么意思？
Means I won some  bowling awards.
意思是我赢过些比赛
I won the marshall H.
我因关于George John罗曼史
Dixon award for my paper  on george john romanes
和生理筛选
and physiological selection.
赢过marshall H.Dixon奖
My god,it's like we lead  parallel lives.
听上去我们的生活像平行线一样
Need shoes?
要鞋子吗
Yeah.Looking for the manager.
找你们经理
Ted mcgruder.
Ted mcgruder
-Fbi,huh? -Yeah.
-Fbi? -对
We're investigating the death  of one of your employees.
我们在调查你一名员工的死
-Warren granger. -Warren?
-Warren granger -Warren?
When he didn't show up for  his last paycheck,
在他上个发薪日没来的时候
I thought he'd just found  another job
我觉得他找到了其他工作
and didn't want to give notice.
所以没注意到
He was weird like that.
他那样很奇怪
Good kid,though.
不过是个好孩子
Ted,I talked to 'em,but they  just keep giving me lip.
Ted我和他们说过了  但是他们老是戏弄我
Luce,these people are with the fbi.
Luce 这些人是fbi
They're here about warren granger.
他们来这里是为了warren granger
Warren? What about him?
Warren? 他怎么了?
-He's deceased. -Oh,my god.
-他死了 -我的天
-I told you he didn't quit. -I was wrong.
-我告诉过你他没跳槽 -我错了
This is my wife,lucy.
这是我的妻子 lucy
-Sorry. -That's ok.
-对不起 -没关系
how often do those kids  come in here?
那些孩子多长时间来这里一次？
Who,those jokers?
那些人?
Weekends,mostly,
大部分是周末
but they used to come  in a lot more,
但是他们更常常
but in these crazy costumes.
穿者疯狂的戏服来
I told 'em I'd allow it on  halloween,but that's it.
我说过我只允许他们在万圣节穿
Is warren's girlfriend here?
warren的女朋友在这里吗？
We were informed that warren's  girlfriend worked here.
我们了解到warren's deceased  的女朋友在这里工作
Well,I mean, f you ever met warren,
如果你认识warren的话
you'd know he's not the  girlfriend type of kid.
你就知道他不是那种会交女友的孩子
There was a girl who came by  to see him sometimes.
有时会有个女孩来看他
Yeah. Yeah,that's-that's her.
对 就是她
I-I don't know her name, but...
我不知道她的名字 但是...
I don't think warren was all  that glad to see her,
我不认为warren看到她很高兴
and if she called,he'd ask me  to tell her that he wasn't here.
如果她打电话来  Warren会让我告诉她他不在
brennan.
Maybe he was trying dodge her.
也许他只是想躲避她
Excuse me just one moment, please.
抱歉 我离开以一下
Okay,slow down,zack, and repeat that.
慢点zack 重复一遍
Hypercellularity with total  effacement of the marrow space.
在骨髓空间里完全找不到细胞存在
-Osteoblasts at 26%. -Okay,good work,zack.
-成骨细胞则有26%. -干的不错 zack.
Keep working on the  weapon I.D.
继续认证凶器
I take it we're not going to
我觉得
be getting any bowling in  tonight,huh?
今晚不能打保龄球了 是吗？
Zack said that if warren hadn't  been murdered two months ago,
Zack说即使Warren两个月前没有被谋杀
he'd be dead by now.
现在他也死了
When you said warren was sick  as a child,
当你说Warren是和生病的小孩
you meant leukemia?
你是说白血病？
Yes,
是的
but by the time he was 11, he was in remission.
但是在他11岁的时候 他已经康复了
The hypercellular activity i saw
就我看来 这种细胞运动
only exists in advanced  cancer cases.
只存在于高级癌症中
He must have been very ill.
他的病情一定很严重
You didn't notice?
你们没有发觉吗？
We tried to be there for  warren,but...
我们试着和Warren在一起
he wouldn't let us in.
但是他不让我们进去
Right when you thought
就当你想
you'd built a bridge of trust, he'd quit on you.
建立信任的桥梁时 他却不允许你这么做
He quit trying to face reality.
他不想面对现实
Maybe your son didn't want you  to have to face it.
也许你的儿子不想去面对
He knew his situation was dire,
他知道自己的情况很可怕
and he decided to tough it  out on his own.
然后决定忽视它
Yes.
是的
He saw what it did to me  the first time.
先前他知道它对我造成了多大伤害
It's not that he quit.
不是他退却
It's that he didn't want me  to suffer.
所以他不想让我伤心
You told her that her son  didn't tell her
你告诉她她的儿子不告诉她
about being sick to make her feel better.
是因为想让她好受
But you don't really  believe that.
但你不真这么认为
Well,people don't actually  do that.
人们不会这么做的
So,you just told her that  to make her feel better?
你这么说只是让她好过点？
Right.
对
So,you just did what you  said people don't do.
所以你说了一件人们不太做了事
I wonder why he didn't  tell his mother.
我在想他为什么不告诉自己的母亲
Well,maybe he was all caught  up in the romance of being
也许他只是幻想着
a dying superhero,you know? Adolescent angst,all that.
作为一个英雄去牺牲生命 或者是由于青少年忧郁症什么的
What do you really think?
你到底是怎么想的？
The truth is,I think the boy  was looking how to be a man.
事实上 我认为这个孩子只是想学会做一个真正的男人
All on his own, without any help.
独自 不用任何帮助
He was doing the best  that he could.
他在尽自己所能去做
Heroes don't whine about  being sick.
英雄不会因为生病而哀号
Something like that.
就像这样
Poor kid.
可怜的孩子
Did they know  about the leukemia?
他们知道白血病么？
No,he kept it a secret.
没有 他没说
Tough guy,huh?
是个硬汉子
You were right on before about
你对于那个孩子对于面对
the kid kning he was facing  imminent death.
死亡的恐惧是对的
This changes motivation.
这改变了动机
-The killer's motivation? -No.Warren granger'S.
-杀手的动机? -不 是Warren granger的
You think he was emboldened  by the knowledge
你是说他因为知道
that he was going to die.
自己会死所以胆子变得很大？
He went looking for a fight.
他出去找人打架
He went looking for the twisted.
他去寻找twisted
Wait.No,wait.
等一下等一下
We are allowing the comic  book story
我们太过于注重漫画
to generate too  many hypotheses.
来形成假设
I only heard the  "go get the bad guy" hypothesis.
我只了解到“抓坏人”的假设
It's too general.
太普遍了
Yes,perhaps,the opalescence  represented warren's better nature,
也许opalescence代表了warren好的一面
and the twisted was a reflection  of his darker sexual impulses.
twisted则是他阴暗面的体现
A theme I assume is common  in teenage fiction.
一个在青少年小说里很流行的主题
And the drawings...
那些图画...
hello... bones.
Hello... bones
The drawings.
那些画
Warren wrote the comics,
Warren编了那些漫画
but there was no evidence in his  room that he knew how to draw.
但是他的房间里并没有证据证明他会画画
Dr.Brennan,I found an extra piece  of bone i can't account for.
Brennan教授 我找到了一块多余的骨头
Someone else drew the comic.
画漫画的另有其人
-Stew ellis. -What about him?
-Stew ellis. -他怎么了?
Look.
看
Warren granger wrote this  comic book,
Warren granger写了这本漫画
but it was drawn by stew ellis.
但是是stew ellis画的
Look,I told you,I knew warren  from the store,okay?
我告诉过你了warren 是我在店里认识的
-He was a serious investor. -Did he owe you money,stew?
-他是个认真的投入家 -他欠你钱吗 stew?
-What? -Was it,uh,creative differences,
-什么? -是因为创造性的不同
or was it you just didn't get  enough credit?
还是你没有得到一定的信任？
no,it was none of that.
都不是
Look,why didn't you tell me  you were partners
为什么我早些时候问你
when I asked you earlier?
你不告诉我你们是搭档？
'Cause we had a big argument,
因为我们吵了一大架
and I didn't want you to  think I had a motive.
我不想让你觉得我有动机杀人
Okay.What did you argue about?
你们在吵什么?
Abigail zealey?
No,man.Just merchandising.
不是 只是销售
You argued about merchandising?
你们在吵销售额？
Yeah,warren thought he deserved  70% for the concept,
warren他应拿70% 因为是他想出的情节
but I think,since I did the  actual drawings,I...
但是我认为 因为实际是我在画 所以...
-do you have a publisher? -No.
-你们找到出版商了？ -没有
And now we never will.
现在我们永远不会了
Look,if-if you think that  I killed warren,
如果你认为我杀了Warren
I'm not that stupid,man.
我没有那么笨
So,who do you think killed warren?
那你认为谁杀了warren?
I don't know,man. Definitely not me,okay?
我不知道 但肯定不是我
Well,you know,stew, as of this moment,
stew 现在你在案子里
you're the prime suspect  in warren's murder.
是主要嫌疑犯
-Why? -Why?
-为什么? -为什么?
Because you lied about your  relationship with warren,
因为你关于你和warren的关系撒了谎
so,if I were you,I would think  really,really hard
如果我是你 我会很认真地考虑
if there's anything else you  haven't told me.
是不是还有其他事你没有告诉我
All right,abby.
好吧 abby
Abby?
Triangle.
三角恋
Look,I hooked up with her  a few times,
我追过她几次
but she was obsessed  with warren.
但是她对Warren太痴迷了
-So,you did argue about her. -No,man.
-所以你们还为她争论过 -不是
Warren never wanted abby.
Warren 从来都不想要abby
Okay,maybe it made you jealous  that she wanted him?
也许她喜欢他让你吃醋了？
Dude,abby's cute in a  chick-geek kind of way,
Abby因为有点奇怪所以才可爱
but she's definitely not  that kind of betty
但她可不是那种
you go to the death  chamber for.
你能为她死的女人
Okay,stew,you know what?
Stew 你知道吗？
You're just one of those guys who's  just way,way too good at lying.
你就是那种很在行撒谎的人
Dude,I'm an artist. What do you want?
我是个艺术家
I found the extra piece of  bone lodged here
我找到了在这里的多余骨头
in the odontoid process of c2.
在C2过程中
I-I went through all the  chipping and damage again,
我重新来了一遍切片和拆粉分
but I can't find  where it came from.
但还是找不到它是从哪里来的
Well,it's not from a  cervical vertebrae.
这不是颈部脊椎
-Oh,it's not? -It's from a long bone.
-不是吗? -是长骨的一部分
Probably the deltoid  process of a humerus.
也许是肱骨
Arm bone?
臂骨?
I need you to set up  the microtome
把超薄切片机准备好
and get me paraffin  and an embedding mold.
还有石蜡和模具
Are you going to  prep your own bone slide?
你想自己准备的骨头幻灯片？
Yes.
是的
Usually I do that for you.
通常是我帮你做的
This is a tough one,zack.
这有点难 zack.
The piece is small,
东西很小
and I need to make sure  there's enough left
而且我得保证有足够的留下来
for a dna sample.
作为DNA样本
Warren granger's arm bones  are complete.
Warren granger的臂骨是完全的
This extra bone fragment  didn't come from warren granger.
这多出来的骨头不是warren granger的
Warren granger was the victim  of a violent attack.
Warren granger是暴力袭击的受害者
He fought back.
他有回击
It's possible that during  that struggle,
在争斗的过程中
he struck his attacker  with the same weapon
也许他用同一个武器攻击对方
that was later used to kill him.
然后被这个武器杀死
Which means that piece of bone  could have come from his murderer.
意味着这片骨头可能是凶手的
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
breathing on the sample  dissipates static electricity
像样本呼气防止静电
and makes it easier to cut.
让它好切点
You seem nervous.
你看上去很紧张
If I get this right, I'll be able to tell you
如果成功了 我就可以告诉你
the age,sex and race of  warren granger's killer.
杀害warren granger凶手的年龄 性别和种族
Stew was the artist.
Stew是那个画家
Really?
真的？
You think he killed warren  over artistic differences?
你认为他杀了warren因为艺术上的分歧？
He also had a thing for abby.
他还对abby有好感
Yeah,for a recluse, warren gnger--
总之 warren gnger--
he had his thumb  in a lot of pies.
在很多事情里都掺了一脚
You said before that warren  reminded you of me.
你之前说过warren很像我
You think I'm just like him.
你说我像他
That he hid from life by  immersing himself
用沉浸在自己的世界里来逃避生活
in a fantasy world where  he fought crime,
在那里他可以为正义而战
and I do the same thing, only I don't have superpowers.
我也是在做一样的事 但是我没有超能力
I... I have science.
我... 我有科学
No,bones,you do fight crime.
不 bones 你是在为正义而战
It's not a fantasy.
这不是幻想
And as far as any normal  person is concerned,
就正常人来看
you do have superpowers.
你是有超能力
You're just being nice to me.
你只是在安慰我罢了
-No,I don't do that. -Yes,you do.
-不 不是 -你是
You lied to  warren granger's mother
你对warren granger的母亲撒谎
to make her feel better.
为了让她觉得好点
That seems to  be your superpower.
这看上去像是你的超能力
Look,this piece of bone  you're analyzing--
你现在在分析的骨头
how did it get lodged  in warren granger's neck?
它为什么会跑到warren granger的脖子上去？
It was deposited  by the same weapon
它是被相同的武器打下来的
that severed his  spinal cord.
痕迹一样
Doesn't make it  the killer's bone.
这就不是凶手的骨头了
You thinking a-
你认为-
-a separate murder victim? -The opalescence?
-是另一个受害者? -opalescence?
The woman he loved?
他爱的女人?
-Don't think she's dead. -Why?
-我不认为她死了 -为什么？
This is an arm bone.
这是臂骨
Has anyone we've seen on this  case been favoring her arm?
这个案子中我们见到的人有手臂受伤的吗？
Not that I've noticed.
我没注意到
That's because you're not  an anthropologist.
因为你不是一个
With superpowers.
有超能力的人类学家
That's good.
不错
hello.
你好
Any news about warren?
有有关warren的消息吗?
We're still in the initial  phase of our investigation.
我们还在最初的调查中徘徊
Listen,mr.Mcgruder,you didn't  happen to keep that,uh,
Mcgruder先生 你有没有保留
last payroll check  for warren granger
warren granger的薪水支票
-that you told me about? -By law I have to,yeah.
-就是你和我说的那个? -法律上我得保存
You mind digging that  out for us?
你能帮我们找一下吗？
I mean,I apologize for  the inconvenience.
我很抱歉给你带来不方便
I guess.It's probably  in the file somewhere.
我猜应该在某个文件里
What do you need the  paycheck for?
你为什么要支票？
Ah,it's technical.
技术上的
Mrs.Mcgruder,
Mcgruder太太
what's wrong with  your left side?
你的左手怎么了？
Why would you ask me that?
你为什么要这么问？
I noticed how you held yourself  the last time I was here.
我注意到上次来的时候你也是这样
I didn't think anything of it.
我现在什么都不了解
Though viewed through the  current context,I...
如果单凭表面现象 我...
what is she talking about?
她在说什么?
She wants to know  how you hurt yourself.
她想知道你是怎么受伤的
You' walk as though your  left ribs are cracked.
你走路的姿势看上去左肋骨断了
Also,you favor your left arm.
而且你还护着自己的左手
Oh,I,um...
我...
I-I...fell on the lanes.
我...在小路上跌倒了
They're very slippery.
路很滑
Falling would bruise  a number of ribs.
跌倒会弄断很多肋骨
You're favoring only  one or two.
但你只护着一两根
Type of damage done  by a fist.
应该是拳头造成的
Look, were you and warren close?
你和warren很亲密吗？
He was a nice kid.
他是个好孩子
A really nice kid.
真的很好
Here it is.
在这里
You two want to bowl  a few frames?
你们想打一两回吗？
Got some empty lanes.
还有空跑道
I'll see you in the comic  books,buster.
我会在漫画书里见到你的 混蛋
What?
什么？
Thanks.I'll get this  back to you.
谢谢 我会把这个还给你的
It's,"see you  in the funny pages."
应该是“see you in the funny pages."
Okay,I took a liberty. Her husband beats her.
我有些冲动 但她的丈夫打她
Bones,all right, talk about multiple hypotheses.
Bones讨论以下多种可能
It's a leap,yes, but it was bound to happen.
跳得太快了 但是事情一定是这样的
Me spending so much time  with you.
我和你在一起这么长时间你应该知道
I mean that as a compliment.
我在赞美你
Okay,so warren's former boss  is the twisted,
那你说warren的前老板是Twisted
and the boss' wife is  the opalescence.
老板的妻子是opalescence
-Go back and arrest him. -It's not enough.
-回去逮捕他 -不够
Okay,for that we need something  just a little bit more real.
我们得需要稍微真实点的东西
-Evidence. -Cold hard facts,baby.
-证据 -铁证据 Baby
Dr.Brennan,
Brennan教授
based on your histology  and the dna,
鉴于你提供的组织和DNA
the bone chip found in  warren granger's neck
在warren granger脖子上的骨头碎片
came from a caucasian male, mid 30s.
是高加索男子 30岁
Mcgruder.
Mcgruder
Can you get any more specific?
你能拿到更详细的证据吗？
We need the weapon.
我们要找到凶器
I can get a warrant, search the mcgruder house
我可以拿个搜查证 搜mcgruder的房子
-for whatever you want. -That's the trouble--
-你可以尽情地找 -可是--
we don't know exactly  what we're looking for.
我们根本不知道要找什么
We hit a dead end trying  to reverse engineer it
我们走了死胡同
from the mark on the neck.
试图从头颈上的痕迹来找凶器
Too much damage  and fragmentation.
有太多破坏和碎裂
Wait,you said that in books
你说通过书
you could find  the real world version.
你可以找到一个生活中的真实场景
Yeah,well,I mean...
我是说...
if you know you, it's pretty obvious.
就你来说 这就很明显
-Well,give me an example. -Okay,well,in your book,
-给我举个例子 -在你的书里
your partner's a former  olympic boxer
你的搭档是个前奥林匹克拳击手
who graduated from harvard  and spoke six different languages.
从哈佛毕业 可以说六门语言
In real life...
真实生活中...
you got me.
是我
So what you're saying is...
你是在说...
that reality falls far, far short of the fictional.
现实与小说相差很远
Yeah.Thanks a lot,bones.
对 太感谢了 bones.
Warren granger's spinal cord  was severed by something sharp,
Warren granger的脊髓线是被很锋利的东西摧毁的
but not a knife.
但不是一把刀
If it wasn't a knife, what was it?
如果不是刀 那是什么？
The closest match i could find  would be a corkscrew
我找到最接近的是一把拔塞钻
or a tibetan skull knife.
或藏族颅骨刀
But neither of them explain  how foreign bone
但是这些都不能解释外来的骨头
was left lodged in the vertebrae.
是怎么留在脊椎边缘的
Pull up citizen 14's weapons, ange.
描绘一下citizen 14的武器 ange
It was a boomerang thing, like a sonic gun.
是个可回旋的东西 像声波枪
A laser cutlass.
激光短弯刀
That thing that allowed him  to hear through walls.
能让他透过墙壁听声音
We're looking for something  that has
我们在找的是
a drabber,more banal version  in the real world.
一个实物 在现实中更切实的东西
Why would he be killed  by his own weapon?
为什么他会被自己的武器杀死？
Well,because he probably  had it on him
因为在他和ted mcgruder起冲突的晚上可能把它带在身上
the night he decided to  confront ted mcgruder.
他可能把它带在身上
Citizen 14's arsenal.
Citizen 14的武器
What's that?
这是什么?
That's his main weapon.
这是他的主要武器
It's a three-sided throwing  knife that returns to him.
是三面刀 可以回旋回来
But none of them make  the wounds that resemble
没有一个和Warren的伤口
the one that severed warren's  spinal cord.
和Warren的伤口一致
it was just an idea.
这只是一个想法
Bones...
I fell into the exact thing  that I warned you about--
我掉入了之前提醒过你们的地方--
developing too many hypotheses  not grounded in fact.
不根据实际而推导出太多假设
No,bones,I know exactly  which drab real world thing
不 Bones 我很清楚地知道是什么真实武器
was used to murder warren granger.
杀了warren granger
All this kid wants is to  feel like a hero.
这孩子只是想感觉像个英雄
Suddenly he's facing a damsel  in distress.
突然他碰上了一个悲惨的女孩
Lucy mcgruder is  ten years older.
Lucy mcgruder比他大了10岁
No,it's not the damsel part  that matters.
女孩不重要
It's the distress that appealed  to the kid,you know.
是悲惨的经历吸引了这孩子
Look,it wasn't about the sex  or the romance,it never was.
和性或者爱情都没有关系
He wanted to make a difference  in the world before he died.
他想在死前改变些什么
I told you he was more  like you than me.
我说过你比我像他
-22-705,dispatch. -22-705.
-22-705 回答 -22-705
Unit sent to the  suspect's residence
已经派小组到达疑犯的住处
reports that the domicile  is empty.
住所是空的
No one's there? What about the wife?
没有人在？那他的妻子呢？
Negative. Search team is inside the house.
否定 搜查小组已经进去了
It's empty. Signs of flight.
房子空了 好象出门旅行了
Affirmative,dispatch.
确认收到
He beats her,but she takes off with him anyway?
她打了他 她却和他一同逃跑？
Spousal abuse syndrome.
婚姻虐待综合症
-Dispatch,22-705. -Dispatch.
-这里是22-705. -收到
Can you send a backup unit to  capital bowl 1123 seboldt.
你能派一个小组去1123  Seboldt的保龄球馆吗？
Domestic disturbances  are always weird,okay?
家庭暴力一向都很奇怪
You know,the woman gets beat  on by her husband,
一个女人被丈夫打了后
the cavalry turns up to save her.
骑士上前去拯救她
You know,you'd think she'd be  on the same side as the rescuers,
你也许觉得她是站在援救者一边的
but sometimes...
但有时候...
you're saying watch out  for the wife.
你是说得小心她的妻子
All I'm saying is just stay  alert,okay,bones?
我只是说保持警惕 好吗 Bones?
Okay.
好的
-Ed,why are we doing this? -Shut up.
-Ed 你为什么要这么做？ -闭嘴
You didn't do anything.
你什么都没有做
Lucy,I swear to god, if you don't shut up...
Lucy 我发誓 如果你不闭嘴
I know you wouldn't  hurt warren.
我知道你不想伤害Warren
Of course he would. You see,that's what he does.
他当然会 也就是他所做的
He loves to beat up people  weaker than him.
他喜欢殴打比他弱小的人
-We are closed. -You left your door unlocked.
-我们关门了 -你没有锁门
Probably an oversight due to  your state of panic.
也许是因为你太紧张所以忘了
Yeah,light's were on. We suspected a robbery.
是的 灯没有关 我们以为有抢劫
-Say,have a bevel knife? -A what?
-你有斜角刀吗？ -什么？
It's a triangular  three-sided knife.
是三角形的三面刀
You know,to clean out  bowling ball holes.
清扫保龄球洞用的
Say,I used to have  one back in the day.
我以前有一把
You wouldn't happen  to have one around here,
这里不会凑巧有一把吧
-would you now? -You need a warrant...
-有么？ -你需要搜查证...
you need a warrant to  take any of my stuff.
要拿我的东西你需要搜查证
Lucy,we need a bevel knife.
Lucy 我们需要一把斜角刀
-We keep one in here. -Shut up,lucy!
-我们这里有一把 -闭嘴 lucy!
Why don't you smack her around  a little bit there,ted,huh?
你为什么不打她呢 Ted?
Keep your woman in line.
让她首本分
Yeah.
对了
This could have done it.
这个可以
Say,bones,that bone chip, uh...second victim or murderer?
Bones 那个金发女的  是第二受害者还是...
For warren's sake, I hope it was the murderer.
替warren着想 我希望她是凶手
Me,too.
我也是
What are you talking about? Just get out of here.
你们在说什么 滚
-It'd be his left arm. -What?
-应该是他的左臂 -什么？
Warren was right-handed,
Warren是用右手
so the wound would be  on your husband's left arm.
伤应该在你的左手上
Oh,my god.
我的天
Bones...
right there.
就在这里
I got him,I got him, I got him,I got him.
我抓住他了
Aw,hell,bones,it looks like  you opened up an old wound there.
bones 上去你弄开了一个老伤口
All right,let's go.
好吧  我们走
You know what, you're under arrest.
你被逮捕了
I really hate a wife beater, I really do.
我很讨厌打妻子的人 真的
Almost as much as I hate  someone who kills a dying kid.
几乎和杀了一个重病的孩子 的人一样恨
Warren knew  what ed did to you.
Warren知道Ted对你做了什么
-Did you tell him? -I didn't have to.
-你告诉他的? -我不必说
He saw one night. ed hit me,and...
一天晚上 他看见Ted打我 然后...
warren...
warren ran away.
warren逃走了
Why didn't you go to  the police?
你为什么不报案？
Because... it's not all the time.
因为...不是一直都这样的
It's just when things go bad  and he's under a lot of strain.
只有当事情不妙他又有很大压力的时候
Ted has a bad temper.
Ted的脾气不好
Warren wanted to rescue you.
Warren想救你
Oh,my god
我的天
He probably just wanted to  intimidate your husband.
他也许只是想吓吓你的丈夫
Stop him from attacking you.
让他停止伤害你
Warren stabbed your husband  in the arm with the bevel knife.
Warren用斜角刀刺入你丈夫的左手臂
Ted took the knife away  from warren.
Ted从warren那里把刀抢走
It wouldn't have been hard.
这不会很难
The boy was very ill.
这男孩病很重
After that, it's like you said--
之后 就像你说的――
your husband has a bad temper.
你的丈夫脾气不好
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync: YTET-bayang23 -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:marcella 校对:小 多 时间轴:YTET-bayang23
Bones Season 1 Episode 12
[识骨寻踪]-[BONES] 第一季 十二集 -=END=-